crazysales.com.au 2016-06-24

# CrazySales Privacy Statement

### Effective Date: 2015-05-12

### Introduction to our Privacy Policy

This web site is subject to the National Privacy Principles under the Australian Privacy Act 1988 (as amended by the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000).This privacy policy applies to www.crazysales.com.au owned and operated by Crazy Sales. This Privacy policy explains in general terms how "Crazy Sales", "We", "Us" or "Our" protects the privacy of your personal information under the National Privacy Principles. It will apply to any personal information you provide to us when registering with us on our Web site www.crazysales.com.au. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Crazy Sales has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site:[www.crazysales.com.au](http://www.crazysales.com.au/), and does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. 

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

The types of personal information that we collect from you will depend on the circumstances of collection and on the type of service you request from us. For example, when you wish to purchase a product from this website we may collect details such as your name, address, delivery address, telephone numbers, gender, age and other information relevant to your purchase.

As we are required by law to obtain your consent to the collection of "sensitive information" (such as credit card information), we will assume that you have given consent to the collection of all information you have provided to us for use in accordance with this Statement, unless you tell us otherwise.

### Third Party E-Commerce Solutions Provider

Our shopping cart is hosted by our e-commerce solutions provider. They host our ordering system, and collect your billing information directly from you for the purpose of processing your order. This company does not use this information for any other purpose.

### How We Collect Information

We may collect personal information about you when you visit our website, when you deal with us over the telephone, send us correspondence (whether by letter, fax or email), or when you have contact with us in person. We will not collect any personal information without your consent. We consider that your consent is granted when you complete the fields necessary to facilitate a transaction through this website.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We generally collect your personal information for the following purposes:

?To facilitate your access to our website, products and services

?To deliver products you have ordered from us

?To conduct marketing activities

?To provide you with information about our products and services

?To seek your opinion on our products, services, marketing and website.

?To send you newsletters 

Some of the personal information we collect is essential for us to be able to accurately identify who is using the service. Other types of personal information we collect help us to develop a profile of who is using our service and what their interests are. This assists us in offering products to suit the needs of the users of this website.

### Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of which the information was collected, or for related purposes. For example to complete a transaction on your behalf or provide you with a product that you purchased. We engage third party contractors to perform services for us which involve the contractor handling personal information we hold. For example, we currently engage third party contractors to:

?Deliver products purchased from this website

?Provide electronic funds transfer services, credit card account processing and related services

In these situations, the third party contractor is strictly prohibited from using any personal information about you outside of the specific purpose for which we have supplied it. We may also disclose your personal information to various law enforcement agencies and governments around the world for security, to comply with a subpoena, customs and immigration purposes. Other than the above, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent unless disclosure is either necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, authorised or required by law, reasonably necessary to enforce the law or necessary to investigate any suspected unlawful activity.

If Crazy Sales is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

### Access & Correction of Information About You

We will, on request, provide you with access to the information we hold about you, unless there is an exception which applies under the National Privacy Principles, including for the purposes of correcting or updating that information. We may recover from you our reasonable cost of supplying you with access to this information. Your request to provide access to this information will be dealt with within in a reasonable time. If we refuse to provide you with access to the information, we will provide you with reasons for the refusal and inform you of any exceptions relied upon under the National Privacy Principles.

### Keeping Your Personal Information Up To Date

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete, and up-to-date whenever we collect or use it. If the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date, please contact us and we will take reasonable steps to either correct this information, or if necessary, discuss alternative action with you.

### Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personal Information

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may delete, correct, or update it by accessing our member information page, by emailing our Customer Support at [info@crazysales.com.au](mailto:info@crazysales.com.au), or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

### Choice/Opt-Out

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletters or marketing emails by filling in the Unsubscribe Form, contacting us at [info@crazysales.com.au](mailto:info@crazysales.com.au) or clicking an unsubscribe link that is included in each email.

###  Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Crazy Sales and our partners (such as bloggers, used for promotional or marketing purposes), affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users? movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users? settings (e.g. language preference), and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

### Local Storage Object (Flash /HTML5)

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). 

### Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Crazy Sales stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [info@crazysales.com.au](mailto:info@crazysales.com.au) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

### Collection of 3rd Party PII

You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name, phone number and physical address. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided. 

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Crazy Sales. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

### Blogs

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [info@crazysales.com.au](mailto:info@crazysales.com.au). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

### Live Chat

We may use a live chat feature to assist you with customer services. If our chat feature is offline we will collect your name and email address so that we may reply to your request. We will email you a full live chat history at end of live chat service.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, Google Plus, or Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that may run on our site from time to time. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as post code).

### Security of Your Personal Information

We will securely hold your personal information and we will not trade, rent or sell it.

We will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you. Personal information may be stored both electronically on our computer system, and in hard-copy form. Firewalls, SSL encryption, passwords, anti-virus software and email filters act to protect all our electronic information.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [info@crazysales.com.au](mailto:info@crazysales.com.au)

We take all necessary measures to ensure the security of hard-copy information.

Once your transaction is finalised, both the electronic and hard-copy information are securely archived. After a period of 7 years, both the electronic and hard-copy information will be destroyed. 

### Data Retention

If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at [info@crazysales.com.au](mailto:info@crazysales.com.au). We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Resolving Your Concerns

If you wish to gain access to your personal information, have a complaint about a breach of your privacy or you have any query on how your personal information is collected or used please forward your request, complaint or query to the address below. We will respond to your query or complaint as soon as possible. 

Email: info@crazysales.com.au  
Fax: (03) 9548 0779  
Post: The Privacy Officer, 2/5 Brear St, Springvale VIC 3171. 

### Changes to This Privacy policy

We may amend this Privacy policy as our business requirements or the law changes. Any changes to this Privacy policy will be updated on www.crazysales.com.au, so please visit this page periodically to ensure that you have our most current privacy policy.

If we make any material changes we will notify by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.
